Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, 1967-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1967-1993, I.; Item 1-149
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 209, 25 June 1977, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Shadows... / B. C. E. Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Nora Post, oboe; Martha Hannemann, soprano; Paul Schmidt, speaker; Thomas Halpin, violin; Baird Contemporary Ensemble Recording locat
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_209_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_209_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_209_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_209_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_209_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_209_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_209_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_209_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_209_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_209_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 210, 3 October 1980, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Shostakovitch Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Hartford Chamber Orchestra; Daniel Parker, conductor Recording location: Lincoln Theater (Hartford, Conn.) Source of the Krenek recordings is not known Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 210)
    Contents: Shostakovich: Concerto no. 1; Krenek: Sketches -- Valse lente
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_210_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_210_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_210_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_210_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_210_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_210_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_210_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_210_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_210_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_210_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 211, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Mantra - Stockhausen Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Dolby B Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 211)
    Contents: Stockhausen: Mantra 1-8, 9-17
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_211_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_211_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_211_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_211_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_211_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_211_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 212, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Sierra, Monk, Zappa Performers: Meredith Monk, voice; N. Tilles, piano; G. Bouwhuis, Anthony de Mare, piano; New London Chamber Choir, James Wood, conductor; Sara Stowe, soprano; James Wood, percussion; Eva Nordwalls, harpsichord; Kathleen Jones, clarinet Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 13 (Box 5, Item 212)
    Contents: Monk: Double fiesta; Zappa: Sad Jane; Sierra: Cantos populares: 1. Canto matutino; 2. Ensueno; 3. Canto nocturno -- Invocaciones: 1. Al guardian de los caminos; 2. Al hacedor de nubes; 3. Al que habita en las tinieblas; 4. Al que guarda las aguas; 5. Al
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_212_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_212_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_212_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_212_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_212_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 213, 7 April 1987, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Tangos Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Works introduced by Mikhashoff Derivative files created: 22 (Box 5, Item 213)
    Contents: Music for a summer night: Unidentified Tangos Sahl; Rudhyar; Burgess
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_213_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_213_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_213_02-11pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_213_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_213_02-11sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 214, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Tangos promo Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Label: Selected tangos for inst. Derivative files created: 8 (Box 5, Item 214)
    Contents: Weill: Tango - Ballade -- Sailor's tango; Brel: Funeral tango; Gade: Jalousie; Krenek: Reverie tango; Nancarrow: ?Tango?; Satie: Tango perpétuel; Thomson: Tango lullaby
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_214_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_214_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_214_01-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_214_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_214_01-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 215, 14 April 1985, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Tangos Hallwalls Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Hallwalls (Museum) (Buffalo, N.Y.) Program entitled: The International tango collection Derivative files created: 28 (Box 5, Item 215)
    Contents: Unidentified tangos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_215_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_215_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_01-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_215_02-15pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_215_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_01-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_215_02-15sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 216, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Tangos: BBC Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Recorded by the BBC Derivative files created: 13 (Box 5, Item 216)
    Contents: Tango collections I and II
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_216_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_216_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_216_02-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_216_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_216_02-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 217, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Tangos NPR Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 1 (Box 5, Item 217)
    Contents: 88 tangos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_217_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_217_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_217_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 218, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Termos Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Termos (Amsterdam, Netherlands) Derivative files created: 3 (Box 5, Item 218)
    Contents: Carrara for piano solo; Expres(s for woodwinds, strings, bass clarinet, pianoforte; Buste for 2 bass clarinets
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_218_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_218_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_218_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_218_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_218_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_218_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_218_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_218_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 219, 15 April 1987, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Transco Tango Performers: Mikhashoff, piano, with members of the Houston Symphony Orchestra, Tobias Picker, conductor Recording location: Transco Tower (Houston, Texas) Derivative files created: 14 (Box 5, Item 219)
    Contents: Rudhyar: Tango d'Antan; Luening: Tango maxixe; Krenek: Johnny tango; Satie: Perpetual tango; Cage: Perpetual tango; Nancarrow: Tango; Weill: Tango ballade; Anonymous; Mikhashoff: El grito; Lehrer: Masochism tango
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_219_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_219_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_219_01-14pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_219_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_219_01-14sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 220, 29 June 1973, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Texas 1973 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Diane Tobola, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; Mary Jungerman, clarinet; David Herbert, oboe Recording location: Taylor Music Hall, Trinity University (San Antonio, Texas) Program entitled: The composer in Texas: A concert of American music: 1948-1972; only half of concert recorded Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 220)
    Contents: Oboe and piano; Mikhashoff: Beggar's songs; Johnson, Hunter: Trio; Benjamin, T.: That old 2nd Viennese School rag
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_220_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_220_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_220_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_220_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_220_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_220_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_220_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_220_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_220_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_220_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 221, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Virgil Thomson #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Recording of rehearsal Derivative files created: 16 (Box 5, Item 221)
    Contents: Thomson: Five Shakespeare songs: 1. Was this fair face the cause?; 2. Take, o, take those lips away; 3. Tell me where is fancy bred; 4. Pardon, goddess of the night; 5. Sigh, no more ladies -- Preciosilla -- Gregorian waltz -- Piano sonata no. 3 -- Three winter portraits -- Five songs of Solomon -- Miss Gertrude Stein as a young girl -- In a bird cage -- Bugles and birds -- Karen Brown waltz -- Pastorale -- Merry-go-round
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_221_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_221_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_221_02-08pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_221_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_221_02-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 222, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Virgil Thomson #2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Recording of rehearsal Derivative files created: 22 (Box 5, Item 222)
    Contents: Thomson: Barcarole -- Tango-lullaby -- Fanfare for France -- Four ladies -- Four winter portraits, 1935: 1. A day dream; 2. Meditation; 3. Hymn; 4. Hunt hymn -- Three French boys -- Three Parisian portraits: Poltergeist; Swiss waltz; Aria: Germaine Hugnet -- For a happy occasion -- Courtship -- At the beach -- Marya Freund -- P.M. Jack -- Jane Bowles -- Molly Davis -- Prelude -- Man of iron -- Dr. Roche
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_222_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_222_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_222_02-11pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_222_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_222_02-11sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 223, 24 January 1989 - 26 January 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson: early and as remembered Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; John Boudler, percussion; David Kuehn, trumpet; Martha Herr, soprano Recording location: Trackmaster studios (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby B For full contents, see commercial CD: Virgil Thomson: Early and as remembered. New Albion records: NA 034. Derivative files created: 4 (Box 5, Item 223)
    Contents: Thomson: In Paris (7 songs) -- At home and abroad (10 songs) -- At the Chelsea hotel (9 songs)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_223_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_223_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_223_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_223_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_223_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_223_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_223_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_223_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_223_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_223_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 224, 24 January 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson 1/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; John Boudler, percussion; David Kuehn, trumpet; Martha Herr, soprano Recording location: Trackmaster studios (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby B Rehearsal recording Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 224)
    Contents: Unidentified works by Virgil Thomson: Takes 1-17, 18-39
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_224_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_224_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_224_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_224_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_224_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_224_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 225, 24 January 1989 - 26 January 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson 2/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; John Boudler, percussion; David Kuehn, trumpet; Martha Herr, soprano Recording location: Trackmaster studios (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby Rehearsal recording Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 225)
    Contents: Unidentified works by Virgil Thomson: Takes 40-65, 66-86
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_225_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_225_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_225_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_225_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_225_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_225_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 226, 24 January 1989 - 26 January 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson 3/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; John Boudler, percussion; David Kuehn, trumpet; Martha Herr, soprano Recording location: Trackmaster studios (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby Rehearsal recording Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 226)
    Contents: Unidentified works by Virgil Thomson: Takes 87-105, 106-135
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_226_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_226_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_226_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_226_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_226_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_226_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 227, 24 January 1989 - 26 January 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson 4/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; John Boudler, percussion; David Kuehn, trumpet; Martha Herr, soprano Recording location: Trackmaster studios (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby Rehearsal recording Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 227)
    Contents: Unidentified works by Virgil Thomson: Takes 136-163, 164-182
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_227_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_227_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_227_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_227_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_227_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_227_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 228, 24 January 1989 - 26 January 1989, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson 5/5 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; John Boudler, percussion; David Kuehn, trumpet; Martha Herr, soprano Recording location: Trackmaster studios (Buffalo, N.Y.) Dolby Rehearsal recording Derivative files created: 2 (Box 5, Item 228)
    Contents: Unidentified works by Virgil Thomson: Takes 183-205, 206-208
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_228_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_228_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_228_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_228_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_228_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_228_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 229, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson and friends Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Dolby Derivative files created: 10 (Box 5, Item 229)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_229_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_229_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_229_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_229_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_229_02-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 230, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Thomson WNYC #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: WNYC (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) Derivative files created: 14 (Box 5, Item 230)
    Contents: Thomson: Portraits: Jane Bowles -- Dennis Russell Davies -- Chorale -- Clair Leonard's profile -- Piano sonata no. 2 -- Piano sonata no. 3 -- Houseman -- Stettheimer parade -- Josiah Lasele -- Jean Ozaine -- At home and abroad
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_230_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_230_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_230_02-07pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_230_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_230_02-07sc.mp3